# **Dawn Calder-Murphy**

07463 071918 • dawn.cm@outlook.com • Stourbridge, West Midlands www.linkedin.com/in/dawn-caldermurphy

#### Personal statement

Having always preferred the creative aspects of my previous roles, I have completed various graphic design, web design, and web development courses online over the past 2 years. I would like to join a company that offers exposure to a range of projects where I can use and develop my new skills. A company with a focus on people or the environment would be ideal, but is by no means essential.

What I currently lack in development or design experience, I make up for with 18 years of varied industry experience. This enables me to more easily relate to clients' processes and needs, which can then be translated into solutions.

## **Key Skills**

- Long-term interest in web development, graphic design and admin functionality, combined with current formal training: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript & Python.
- Excellent verbal, written and telephonic communication skills.
- Highly adaptable in dealing with operational changes, as demonstrated by my varied industry experience.
- · Passionate about giving my all and improving my skill set.

## **Education**

References and Certificates are available upon request

Code Institute codeinstitute.net

Full Stack Web Development - current (2017)

Code School codeschool.com

HTML / CSS Path – current (2018) JavaScript Path – current (2018) Shaping Up with AngularJS lesson – (2018)

Shaw Academy.com

Smartphone Photography
October 2016
Foundation in Web Design
September 2016
English for Business
August 2016
Advanced Graphic Design
Foundation in Web Development
Foundation in Graphic Design
Foundation in Mobile App Development
April 2016
April 2016

GoSkills goskills.com

Trello December 2017 Adobe Illustrator - Basic October 2017 **Project Management Basics** August 2016 Writing Effective Business Communications March 2016 Microsoft Outlook February 2016 Microsoft Excel Basic & Advanced January 2016 Microsoft Word Advanced January 2016 Microsoft Word Basic January 2016

Languages: Duolingo <u>duolingo.com</u> Currently learning: Welsh, Dutch

# **Sussex Partnership NHS Foundation Trust**

Care related courses, since expired due to the high standards required by the care industry.

### **Kimberley Girls High School**

Matriculated 1998 with University Exemption (A-level Equivalent)

kimberleygirlshigh.org.za

# **Employment History**

### Administrative Assistant, Allegis Group, Birmingham UK

March 2017 – August 2017 (3-month fixed term contract, extended once)

allegisgroup.com

#### Responsibilities:

- Bespoke MS Excel reporting
- · Auditing of on-boarding documents and forms
- · General admin tasks as required by the Customer Support teams in various regional offices

### Office Administrator, Dave Pohl & Associates, South Africa

January 2014 - December 2015

davepohl.co.za

#### Responsibilities:

- Liaising with the various financial houses & clients as relevant to new products, amendments & claims.
- Creating or converting forms from paper based to PDF or web based.
- Design of shop signage, banners, and flyers / brochures for networking events.

### Sales Assistant (Maternity Cover Temp), Bargain Books, South Africa

July 2013 – December 2013

bargainbooks.co.za

### Responsibilities:

- Assist customers to find books or gifts, then process cash or credit card sales on POS system.
- Place custom orders via the shop software & supplier websites.
- · Assist with daily cash-ups and banking.

### Bio Sculpture Technician (Merit Exam), Self-employed, South Africa

March 2012 - November 2012, January 2016 - December 2016

biosculpture.co.za

### Customer Accounts Advisor, Hastings Direct, Bexhill-on-Sea, East Sussex

April 2011 - December 2011

hastingsdirect.com

#### Responsibilities:

- Admin and payment duties relating to insurance policy premiums.
- Working through custom exception reports to ascertain any problems on policies, and implementing fixes, or submitting solutions for approval by the relevant department.
- · Compliant with the Data Protection Act.

## **Bank Support Worker:**

Quality Reliable Care, Eastbourne, East Sussex (January 2011 – April 2011) <a href="mailto:qualityreliablecare.co.uk">qualityreliablecare.co.uk</a> Sussex Partnership NHS Foundation Trust, East Sussex (May 2010 – April 2011) <a href="mailto:sussexpartnership.nhs.uk">sussexpartnership.nhs.uk</a>

## Responsibilities:

Provided various levels of support to adults with learning disabilities and challenging behaviours.

# From February 1999 to January 2010 I held several temporary and permanent positions, including:

<ul> <li>Temp Customer Accounts Advisor</li> </ul>	Hastings Direct, UK	<u>hastingsdirect.com</u>
<ul> <li>Accounts Receivable Clerk</li> </ul>	Legend Lodges Hotels & Resorts, SA	legendhospitality.co.za
Working holiday	Dugong Beach Lodge, Mozambique	dugong-beach-lodge
Front Office Assistant	Entabeni Safari Conservancy, SA	entabeni-safari-conservancy
<ul> <li>Rooms Division Manager</li> </ul>		
<ul> <li>Accounts Payable Clerk (Temp)</li> </ul>	Famous Brands Ltd, SA	famousbrands.co.za
<ul> <li>Accounts Payable Clerk (Temp)</li> </ul>	Automobile Association of South Africa	aa.co.za
Accounts Payable Clerk	Protea Hotel Knysna Quays, SA	proteaquays.co.za
Office Manager	GBouwer Transport, SA	
<ul> <li>Client Services &amp; Operational Support</li> </ul>	Personalised Systems & Services, SA	smartcollect.co.za
Receptionist		
<ul> <li>Personal Assistant</li> </ul>	The Kingdom Cultural Resort, SA	
Sales & Production	Creative Metal Images, SA	creativemetalimages.co.za